http://www.melvillewaterpolo.com.au/view/about/privacy-policy-2014

Introduction
1.1 We understand that the privacy of your personal details, and the security of your transactions with us, is important to you, so it is important to us. Melville Water Polo Club Inc ("MWPC") complies with the Privacy Policy of Australian Water Polo, who in turn complies with the "Commonwealth Privacy Amendment (Private sector) Act 2000.
1.2 Should you wish to contact us in relation to Privacy, please email us at office@melvillwaterpolo.com.au, or 5 Durdham Cresent, Bicton, WA, 6157.
1.3 We may make alterations or additions to this policy from time to time. Should we do so, we will update the policy on our website.
1.4 Please note that we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for the privacy or security practices of any other websites which you may be able to link to or access through our site.
2.
What Information Do We Collect?
2.1 MWPC collects different information about you at different times.
2.2 Information we require to supply our services.
2.2.1 When you first sign up or contract with MWPC for our services, or when you make an inquiry about our services, we request information such as your name, address, telephone numbers and email details.
2.2.2 Water Polo Registration information is collected to administer your participation in Water Polo. We need to provide WA Water Polo Inc and Australian Water Polo with some of this information.
2.3 Non personally identifying information.
2.3.1 We may also use 'cookies'. Cookies are pieces of information that a website can transfer to an individual's computer in order to allow that website to store information about user preferences. Cookies are used to collect session IDs. It is possible to adjust your internet browser to refuse cookies, but you may find that this reduces the functionality of this site.
3.
How Do We Use Personal Information We Have Collected?
3.1 We collect and use your personal information to operate our facility and deliver our services to you.
3.2 You may stop the delivery of future promotional email from MWPC by following the specific instructions in the email you receive. These instructions will tell you how to remove your name from our email list.
Show Sitemap
About
About our club
Committee
History
Life Members
Bicton Pool
Club Coaches
Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions | Copyright © 2014 Melville Water Polo Club
